 export const qnAnswerList = [
  {
    id: 1, 
    question: "How many days is normal period come?",
    answer: "The average period is 28 days, but ranges 21 - 35 Days"
 },
 {
    id: 2, 
    question: "Can a woman/girl get pregnant at any time during menstruation cycle?",
    answer: "No, Woman/girl can get pregnant only during ovulation period"
  },
  {
    id: 3,
    question: "Where can you get sexual and reproductive health services and information?",
    answer: "Health medical center, Online, Parents, etc"
  },
  {
    id: 4,
    question: "What is self-exploration?",
    answer: "In the context of sexual health and well-being, self-exploration commonly refers to the practice of individuals learning about their own bodies, preferences, and sexual responses. This can include activities such as masturbation, where individuals engage in sexual self-stimulation for pleasure and self-discovery."
  },
  {
    id: 5,
    question: "Can you offer guidance to your friend on self-exploration if they are considering engaging in sexual activity? Why?",
    answer: "This may vary based on several factors. <small>Refer to the documentation for more infos.</small>"
  },
  {
    id: 6,
    question: "Is it possible for girl/women having sex during menstruation period?",
    answer: "Yes, it is possible. <small>Refer to the documentation for more infos.</small>"
  },
  {
    id: 7,
    question: "What do you understand by term tampon?",
    answer: "A tampon is a feminine hygiene product designed to absorb menstrual blood during menstruation. It is a small, cylindrical-shaped device made of absorbent material, usually cotton, that is inserted into the vagina to manage menstrual flow. Tampons come with an applicator for insertion or can be inserted using the fingers."
  },
  {
    id: 8,
    question: "When do girls enters pubic age and what are some common physical signs appears during the time?",
    answer: "Girls typically experience the onset of puberty between the ages of 8 and 13. Common physical signs include breast development, the widening of hips, the growth of pubic hair, and the onset of menstruation."
  },
  {
    id: 9,
    question: "At what age do boys usually begin to show signs of puberty, and what are some noticeable changes?",
    answer: "Boys usually start puberty between the ages of 9 and 14. Physical signs include the enlargement of the testicles and the development of pubic hair. Additionally, boys may experience a growth spurt, deepening of the voice, increased muscle mass, and the appearance of facial hair."
  },
  {
    id: 10,
    question: "What emotional and psychological changes are commonly associated with puberty?",
    answer: " Adolescents may experience mood swings, increased self-awareness, and a desire for independence. Hormonal fluctuations during puberty can contribute to heightened emotions, ranging from excitement to irritability. "
  }
];